Chronos Policy: Learning Robot Policies on Physical Time. Real robots, Blender, and MuJoCo.
Inference latency. Computation delays the action.
Zoom into Dynamic Cup.
Policy sensitive to inference latency. DP and Chronos Policy, 2× playback.
Zoom back to the inference latency diagram.
Continue on physical time.
Observation timing. Measurements may delay.
Zoom into Peg Insertion.
Policy sensitive to observation and inference latency. DP and Chronos Policy, 2× playback.
Zoom back to the observation timing diagram.
Continue on physical time.
Different sensor rates. Each sensor follows its own clock.
Zoom into Pivoting.
Policy sensitive to sensor-rate changes. DP and Chronos Policy, 2× playback.
Zoom back to the different sensor rates diagram.
Continue on physical time.
Chronos Policy: Learning Robot Policies on Physical Time. A equals f of O expands to include observation capture times and requested action times.